Raul H. Castro papers, 1903-2007 (bulk 1939-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Raul H. Castro papers, 1903-2007 (bulk 1939-2003)
MS 417
Castro, Raul H.
This collection includes material documenting the life and career of educator, attorney, judge, diplomat, and political figure Raul H. Castro. Items include correspondence, law practice files, photographs (color, black & white), negatives (color, black & white), slides (color), news clippings, audiovisual material (including cassette audiotapes, reel-to-reel audiotapes, audio CDs, videocassette tapes, DVDs, and LPs), scrapbooks, and objects (including drawings, paintings, and plaques).
35.75 Linear feet (about 28,750 items)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Raul Hector Castro was born June 12, 1916, in Cananea, Sonora, Mexico. He was one of fourteen children-his father was a copper miner and his mother was a midwife. He lived in Mexico as a child until his family moved to the Douglas, Arizona area in 1926. While attending Douglas High School, Castro played football, edited the school newspaper, and graduated with honors. He then attended Arizona State Teacher's College (now Northern Arizona University) on a football scholarship and was captain of the track team and the boxing team. Known as the "Douglas Destroyer," Castro was an undefeated boxer while in college and he won most of his bouts by knockout. He received a B.A. in education in 1939 and he became a U.S. citizen that same year.
Castro spent the next five years working as a foreign-service clerk for the U.S. State Department in Agua Prieta, Sonora, Mexico. He then moved to Tucson and became a Spanish instructor at the University of Arizona. While at the university, Castro was accepted into the law school. He paid his way through law school by continuing to teach Spanish courses. He earned his law degree and was admitted to the Arizona State Bar in 1949. After spending five years in private practice, Castro was elected Pima County Attorney in 1954. In 1958 he was elected as a Pima County Superior Court judge. He served on the bench until 1964, including three years of service as a juvenile court judge.
In 1964, President Lyndon B. Johnson appointed Castro as U.S. Ambassador to El Salvador. Castro had met and befriended Johnson in 1960 when Johnson made a campaign stop in Tucson as the Democratic vice-presidential candidate. One of the highlights of Castro's ambassadorship to El Salvador was the week-long official visit of President and Lady Bird Johnson to that country in 1968. In the summer of 1968, Johnson appointed Castro as U.S. Ambassador to Bolivia. In 1969, newly-elected President Richard M. Nixon, a Republican, allowed Castro, a staunch Democrat, to retain his appointment as ambassador to Bolivia, attesting to Castro's effectiveness in the position. Nevertheless, Castro wished to return to Arizona and resume his law practice and he departed Bolivia in November 1969.
Castro entered the Arizona governor's race in 1970. He easily won the Democratic primary despite entering the race much later than his primary opponents. He then lost the general election by a small margin to incumbent governor Jack Williams. Castro entered the governor's race again in 1974 and this time he won, defeating Republican candidate Russ Williams and becoming the state's first Latino governor. Castro served as the 14th governor of Arizona from 1975 to 1977. During the 1976 presidential election, Castro supported former governor of Georgia Jimmy Carter. Castro toured with Carter during the 1976 campaign and he spoke at the 1976 Democratic National Convention in New York City, urging the Latino Caucus to lend its support to Carter. Castro's support proved instrumental in Carter's garnering the Latino vote in the Democratic primaries, where Mo Udall was Carter's main opponent, as well in the general election against incumbent President Gerald Ford. In 1977, Castro resigned the governorship of Arizona when President Jimmy Carter offered him an appointment as U.S. Ambassador to Argentina. This ambassadorship posed many challenges: the Argentine economy was in shambles as it suffered runaway inflation and the government was widely accused of human rights abuses. Castro succeeded in maintaining friendly relations between the U.S. and Argentina while putting pressure on the Argentine government to improve its human rights record. He resigned from the ambassadorship in July 1980 and returned to Arizona to resume his law practice.
From 1980 to 2003, Castro's private practice concentrated on the areas of immigration law and international law. Castro retired from his private law practice in 2003. He has been accorded numerous honors over the years, including induction into the Northern Arizona University Sports Hall of Fame as well as receipt of honorary doctorates from Northern Arizona University, Arizona State University, and La Universidad Autonoma de Guadalajara. Also, Arizona Governor Janet Napolitano proclaimed February 16, 2006, as "Raul H. Castro Day" in Arizona. He has been honored by all of the major higher education institutions in Arizona. The Raul H. Castro Institute was established as a collaborative effort between Arizona State University, Phoenix College, and the Maricopa County Community College District. The Institute sponsors policy research regarding the Arizona Latino community. The Raul H. Castro Scholarship is awarded annually to deserving students at the University of Arizona through the Center for Latin American Studies. Also, the Raul H. Castro College of Social and Behavioral Sciences building at Northern Arizona University is named in his honor.
Organization
This collection is organized into eleven series. The Photographic Material series contains four subseries.
Series 1: Biographical Files, 1963-2007
Series 2: Correspondence, 1944-2004 (bulk 1970-1990)
Series 3: Governor's Files, 1967-1978 (bulk 1974-1977)
Series 4: Law Practice Files, 1953-2004 (bulk 1980-2003)
Series 5: Subject Files, 1949-2005 (bulk 1971-1987)
Series 6: News Clippings, 1951-2000 (bulk 1974-1980)
Series 7: Photographic Material, 1939-2003 (bulk undated)
Subseries: Photo Albums, 1977 (bulk undated)
Subseries: Photographs, 1939-2003 (bulk undated)
Subseries: Negatives, 1977 (bulk undated)
Subseries: Slides, 1976
Series 8: Audiovisual Material, 1973-2006
Series 9: Objects, 1964-1980
Series 10: Scrapbooks, 1973-1977 (bulk undated)
Series 11: Oversized, 1903-2007 (bulk 1958-2007)
Scope and Content Note
The Raul H. Castro Papers document his career in public service from his election as a Pima County judge in 1958 through three U.S. ambassadorships (El Salvador 1964-1968, Bolivia 1968-1969, and Argentina 1977-1980) as well as the governorship of Arizona (1974-1977). The collection also contains material highlighting his education and sports activities at Arizona State Teacher's College (now Northern Arizona University), his legal education at the University of Arizona, his private law practice, his family life, and his personal and business interests. The collection is organized into eleven series (one series, Photographic Material, is subdivided into four subseries). The collection contains correspondence, news clippings, subject files, governor files, law practice files, photographic material, audiovisual material, objects, and scrapbooks.
Access Terms
Castro, Raul H., 1916- -- Archives.
Castro, Raul H., 1916- -- Correspondence.
Governors -- Arizona -- Archives.
Arizona -- Politics and government -- 20th century -- Sources.
Arizona -- History -- 20th century -- Sources.
Hispanic American lawyers -- Arizona -- Archives.
Hispanic Americans -- Arizona -- Archives.
Bolles, Don
Container List
- Series 1: Biographical Files 1963-2007
  .75 linear feet (about 750 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  The Biographical Files series contains miscellaneous biographical material relating to Raul H. and Patricia Castro. Included are items regarding Governor Castro's induction into the Northern Arizona University Sports Hall of Fame, and his receipt of honorary degrees. (Note: some folders of biographical files are located in Series 11: Oversized).
  - Affidavit of Raul H. Castro. 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Material. 1976-2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Castro, Patricia. 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Certificates and Awards. 1963-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cochise County Courthouse Diamond Jubilee Celebration. 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ft. Lowell Property (Tucson). 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General. 1970-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General. 2000-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Honorary Degrees. 1967-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Northern Arizona University Sports Hall of Fame Induction. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sketched Certificates. undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1944-2004 (bulk 1970-1990)
  3.75 linear feet (about 2,500 items).
  Arrangement: alphabetical. This series contains personal letters and official letters from Castro's diplomatic career. Political correspondence with notables such as Vice President Nelson Rockefeller, Secretary of State Henry Kissinger, Senator Barry Goldwater, and former Massachusetts governor and presidential candidate Michael Dukakis are included. Some correspondence is in Spanish.
  - Aja Espil, Jorge (Ambassador to Argentina). 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Albanez, Ernestine. 1970-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Archer, Pat. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Argentina. 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Argentina. 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Babbitt, Bruce. 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Barfield, John. 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Basha, Eddie. 1975-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bensusan, Dr. H. Guy (Northern Arizona University). 1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bolivia. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Castro, Patricia M. undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Castro, Patricia M. 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Castro, Patricia M. 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Christmas Cards. 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
  - Christmas Cards. 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - DeConcini, Dennis. 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - De Leon, Armando. 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Drinkwater, Herb. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - El Salvador. 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - El Sol Investment Corporation. 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - General. undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - General. 1947 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - General. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - General. 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - General. 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - General. 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - General. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - General. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
  - General. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 42-43)
  - General. 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - General. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
  - General. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 47-49)
  - General. 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General. 1990-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General. 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gillette, Michael L (Lyndon Baines Johnson Library). 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Goddard, Sam (Arizona State Democratic Committee Chairman). 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Greeting Cards. undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Greeting Cards. 1964-2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Harvey, Christine. 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hate Letters. 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hickey, William M. 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Invitations. undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Invitations. 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Invitations. 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Invitations. 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - Invitations. 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Invitations. 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Invitations. 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Jaro, Sue. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kimball, Richard. 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lippman-Gordon, Marilyn. 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Los San Patricios de Arizona. 2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - MacDonald, Peter. 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Moffard, Rose. 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - New Articles. 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Personal. 1975 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
  - Political. 1960-1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Powell, Minnie Mae (Durfee Awards). 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Rogers, Ginger. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Siderman, Carlos (re: Jose Siderman Kidnapping in Argentina). 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Snelgrove, C. Laird. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Snowflake Unified School District No. 5. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Zipf, Henry. 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Series 3: Governor's Files 1967-1978 (bulk 1974-1977)
  4.5 linear feet (about 3,000 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  The bulk of the material of this series was created during Raul H. Castro's tenure as governor of Arizona, 1974-1977. This series includes correspondence and includes several folders of letters to and from constituents as well as received letters of invitation to speak at and attend official and social events. Also included are several folders containing Patricia Castro's professional correspondence related to her duties as first lady of Arizona. Included are events calendars for Raul and Patricia Castro, financial disclosure statements, newsletters from various Arizona state agencies, information regarding Bicentennial projects, information regarding the U.S.S. Arizona Memorial dedication, and brochures and other publications from various Governors' conferences attended by Raul H. Castro.
  - Ali, Muhammad (Show Low, Arizona). 1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Annual Governors' Conference- A First Lady, Everyone. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Appointment Books. 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
  - Appointment Books. 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Arizona Artists in Action. 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Arizona Board of Regents. 1975 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Arizona Department of Transportation Applications. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Arizona Farm Bureau Federation Annual Meeting Program. 1975 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Arizona Game and Fish Department. 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Arizona Game and Fish Department Wildlife Bulletin. 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Game and Fish Department Wildlife Bulletin. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Motion Picture Development Program. 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arizona Office of Tourism Pamphlet. undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Articles about Castro, Raul. 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Humanities. 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6-12)
  - Asian Goodwill Trade Mission. 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bicentennial Projects. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bobby Ball Memorial Auto Race. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Calendars. 1967-1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Calendars. 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - Calendars. 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - California Border Cities Leadership Conference (San Diego, California). 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Cantu, Armando. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Capital Rotunda Christmas. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Casa Castro (San Carlos, Sonora). 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - "Castro for Governor". 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Castro for Governor". 1974 (Box 3, Folder 25-27)
  - "Castro for Governor" Briefing Materials. 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Castro, Patricia M. (Events). 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2-6)
  - Castro, Patricia M. (Events). 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7-11)
  - Castro, Patricia (Recipes). 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Castro, Patricia (Speeches). 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Cards from Governors. 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Lists. 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Copper License Plate. 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Castro, Patricia M. 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Castro, Patricia M. 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Castro, Patricia M. 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Castro, Patricia M. 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
  - Correspondence - Castro, Patricia M. 1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Castro, Patricia M. 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence - Convention Bureau. 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence - General. 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - General. 1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Governors. 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Governor's Office. 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8-11)
  - Correspondence - Gubernatorial Letters of Congratulation. 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - Correspondence - Gubernatorial Letters of Greeting. 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Invitations. 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15-18)
  - Correspondence - Invitations Regretted. 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Letters from Children. 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
  - Correspondence - Letters of Support. 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Mimeo Mail. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - School Projects. 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Thank You Letters for Gifts. 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Thank You Letters for Gifts. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Critical Hundred Days- A Handbook for the New Governor. 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Del E. Webb Corporation Honduras Claim. 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Department of Public Safety. 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Eighth Floor of State Capital Building Project. 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - El Bosque (Prescott Property). 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Financial Disclosure Statements. 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - First Ladies Bicentennial Traveling Egg Case. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Flag Raising Ceremony at Governor's House. 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Flags. undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Four Corners Regional Commission Annual Report. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fuel Oil Data Briefing Materials. 1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gifts. 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Governor Raul H. Castro Testimonial Dinner. 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Governor's Harvest Ball, Second Annual (Program). 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Governor's Harvest Ball, Third Annual (Program). 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Governor's House Guest Registry. 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Governors of the American States, Commonwealths, Territories. 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Governor's Trust Fund. 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Highway Users Federation. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Ho Luncheon. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Inauguration Ceremony. 1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Inauguration Ceremony (News Clippings). 1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Indianapolis "500". 1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Miss Arizona (Stacey Peterson). 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Miss Arizona Universe Pageant. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Newsletters. 1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Newsletters. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 32-34)
  - Newsletters. 1977 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Official Canvass State of Arizona General Election. 1974 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Official Canvass State of Arizona General Election. 1978 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Office of Economic Planning and Development. 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Polland, Donald. 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Printed Items (Stationary, etc.). 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of the National Governors' Conference. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Property Loaned to the Capitol and State. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Property Loaned to the Capitol and State. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate Proposals. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Realtors. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Requests for Visits. 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Russian Tour. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Staff. 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Taiwan Tour. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Today" Show Interview. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Udall, Morris K. 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - U.S.S. Arizona Medallions. undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - U.S.S. Arizona Memorial. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
  - Valley Democratic Women's Club Luncheon (Carefree, Arizona). 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Western Governors' Conference. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Series 4: Law Practice Files, 1953-2004 (bulk 1980-2003)
  6.0 linear feet (about 4,000 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  The bulk of this series consists of appointment books, telephone memo records, and Arizona state bar publications. The series also contains material regarding Raul H. Castro's "of counsel" status with the New York firm Walsh & Levine and material documenting his participation with the Napolitano for Governor campaign, his involvement with Nogales City Charter Reform, and his appointment to the Arizona State Sentencing and Parity Review Study Committee (he was appointed to the committee in 1993 by Chief Justice Stanley Feldman of the Arizona Supreme Court). Additionally, there is information regarding Raul Castro's representation of Nora Nistor in a high-profile murder case in Tucson (Ms. Nistor was charged with murdering her husband and she relied on the "battered-spouse" defense at her trial). Some items are in Spanish.
  - Aliens (Illegal Entry). 2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Application for Asylum and for Withholding of Deportation (Form I- 589). undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Appointment Books. 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Appointment Books. 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Appointment Books. 1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Appointment Books. 1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Appointment Books. 2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Argentine American Chamber of Commerce, Inc. 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Arizona Ground Water Law: The Need for Legislation" (Arizona Law Review). 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Torts Verdicts. undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Arizona/Sonora Project: Balancing the Future. 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - The Arlin J. Brown Information Center of Phoenix, Inc. 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Castillo V. Burrill. 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - City of Nogales Utility System Purchase. 2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cloning (Legal Issues). 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Community Property Law in Arizona. undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Consumer Choice Coalition. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - Crime & Delinquency (Volume 28, Number 1, January 1982). 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Crime & Delinquency (Volume 31, Number 3, July 1985). 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Derecho Internacional Publico. 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Domestic and Foreign Corporations for Profit. 1959 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dominican Trade Mission. 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - "Economic Impact of the Mexico-Arizona Relationship". 2003 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Employment Inquires. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Evans, Leonard (The Universal Economic and Education Trust). 1996-2004 (Box 8, Folder 19-20)
  - General. 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Good Victory Enterprises Corporation. 1983 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Haim, Marc. 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Historic Building Analysis of the Elias/Rodriguez House (Tempe, Arizona). 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - International Law Section 1996 Directory (State Bar of Arizona). 1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - International Law Section 1998-1999 Directory (State Bar of Arizona). 1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Law Office Stationary. undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Legal Forms. 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Legal Forms (blank). undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Los Abogados. 1988 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Lowe, Elisa Partida. 2003 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - LVO Cable of Tucson, Inc. 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - MacDonald, Peter ("The Pardoning of Peter MacDonald, Sr."). 1993 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Manufacturing in Sonora, Mexico. 1988 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Massious, Peter (Evangelous Restaurant). 2003 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Mexico Telephone Area Codes Directory. 2001 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous. 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous. 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Napolitano for Governor Campaign. 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - National Governors' Association. 1983 (Box 8, Folder 39)